Wait. Time out!
You can't leave.
Alex, I'm not lying to you.
I'm telling the truth that Chiara
is no longer a Moraviano.
There's a tactical squad positioned
right outside this room,
so you have nowhere to run.
Who is La Morte Bianca? Is she even real?
Yes! Of course she is.
If we thought before that the Moravianos
were our only enemies,
we were very wrong.
There's something worse.
There's a bigger force that is about
to descend upon the entire Philippines.
Kare-kare.
You probably think you can fool me
because you're La Fornarina, huh?
You Moravianos are all the same.
I'm not fooling you.
Why don't you first prove to me
that the information
you're offering is valuable?
Then I'll decide whether it's truly worthy
of immunity from prosecution.
Not you being the one making demands.
I know what you're doing.
So annoying.
Can you talk to your girlfriend?
I can make suggestions,
but I could never dictate to her.
Because, you know, Agent Alex,
when it comes to our relationship,
we value, you know,
mutual respect and independence.
We don't have traditional gender roles
because we view each other as equal.
Right?
You need vital information, right?
I can give you that.
But this is a game changer.
Just make sure you're ready.
You talk like it's such a game changer.
Wait, wait. This is not overhype, huh?
Think of it this way,
Agent Alex. In a TV drama,
the information Chiara has
is Book 2 material.
Yes, that's how intense it is.
The kind that keeps you hooked.
So if I were you, give Chiara a chance.
Hear her out first.
They said our salary's in!
Salary today,
just a memory tomorrow.
Well, that's life.
So before it all gets eaten up by bills,
- let's have samgyupsal first.
- Samgyupsal it is.
Samgyupsal.
Because, you know,
we deserve it.
Of course.
But you know,
you guys go ahead.
- Why?
- Nothing. We're not complete.
Look.
General Norberto isn't here
because he's on vacation leave.
And Alex is in Hong Kong.
Well,
it would've been more fun
if we were all here.
- Exactly.
- How about this?
Guys, let's just get burgers.
- The buy-one-take-one deal!
- Let's go.
- Sure, sure, sure.
- What do you mean, let's go?
We're getting burgers.
Hey, wait.
It's Alex. Dara, come on, come on.
Monitor the call.
- Okay.
- Let's head downstairs.
- Let's just wait.
- Okay, let's wait downstairs.
Good thing you finally called.
We've been waiting for your updates.
So much has happened.
There's been a lot going on, Bok.
Okay, okay. But how are things?
Did you catch Chiara and Mikoy?
- Yes, they're with me now.
- Nice!
How are they?
Did La Fornarina attack you or something?
I'm fine.
I eventually cornered them.
More than nice.
I'm so incredibly proud of you, Bok.
You know that?
Because all the hard work
you've put in from the very beginning,
it's all paying off now with this case.
Thank you.
But we still have a long way to go.
Of course, but…
don't think about that for now.
Okay? How about you?
How are you over there?
Are you eating three meals
a day over there?
Are you drinking two liters of water?
And your steps,
are you still hitting 10,000 a day?
Also, isn't it hot in Hong Kong?
The heat index is brutal
here in the Philippines.
- Hey!
- What?
Focus!
Bok, can we save
the catching up for later?
Of course, of course, Bok.
Sorry, we just can't help worrying.
We're worried about you here.
I understand. Thanks for your concern.
I'm okay.
Mario. I'll head out first,
I still have to do my rounds.
- Thank you very much, Chief!
- Okay.
I'll take care of the gate.
I guess you're worried
about Mikoy, aren't you?
Of course.
I don't even know how he's doing.
I do.
You do?
Of course I know something.
You know, even confidential information
finds its way to me.
You know,
the perks of having a father who's
the director general of the agency.
And you're going to share
this information with me?
Of course.
I can feel your concern.
As a matter of fact, here's the latest.
The agency's best agent,
Special Agent Alex,
has already flown to Hong Kong.
And she's already figured out where Mikoy
and Chiara Valtrovi are.
So you think
Agent Alex will find Mikoy?
Knowing Alex, it seems very possible.
I wouldn't be surprised
if right at this moment,
she's already caught both of them.
I hope Mikoy is safe.
I hope so too.
What is this Lazarus Initiative?
Do you really want to know
about Project Lazarus?
Of course!
Okay, fine.
What's the password?
Tori-tori?
Chuva-chuva?
Locco-locco.
Locco-locco!
You silly goose.
But on a serious note.
Here's what Project Lazarus is.
It's a mechanism of the state.
It is only activated
when all criminals need to be granted
legal protection
to help fight all forms
of organized crime.
I don't remember that being
in the employee orientation manual.
That's because it's top secret.
So Project Lazarus
justifies the criminal acts
of the people we're chasing? What?
About this case.
All these organized groups
around the world
are incredibly complex, deeply rooted,
and have vast networks,
including their connections.
Like hitting the jackpot.
But if we ever manage to land a big fish,
we don't want to let
that opportunity slip away.
Especially if they already know things
that no matter how much
undercover work we do,
we would never discover.
Exactly.
I'm exercising.
I'm almost at 10,000 steps.
And it's part of my training too.
Is it because you're
running again in 2028?
Or are you running for a higher office?
No, I don't have any plans. Not yet.
I'm just training in case
I get thrown into something.
Wait a second. Why are you here?
Is it an urgent matter?
G.A.G.O. has called an emergency meeting.
About what?
For the case of the Moravianos.
Judge, meet our good-hearted lover boy,
Mikoy D. Pinagpala.
His heart is so big
for the people he loves
that it seems like everyone
he loves fits inside it.
His family, his neighbors, his friends,
and his sweetheart.
Now that we've met our main character,
let's proceed with the story.
To put his youngest sibling
through school in Manila,
Mikoy didn't hesitate
to try his luck abroad as an OFW.
But when he arrived in Prague,
it wasn't just a great opportunity
waiting for him.
There was also a very beautiful woman.
It’s Chiara Valtrovi.
Half Filipino, half Czech.
Things happened very quickly.
They walked all over Prague.
They spent time together and had drinks.
And they got a little romantic.
Got a little romantic?
They kissed, Judge. You know.
They kissed already?
Of course.
This is a modern love story.
And like so many love stories,
no one would follow it
or look forward to it
without conflict,
because it turns out this beautiful woman
is the only child
of Viktor Valtrovi.
He is the leader of a European mafia
known as the Moravianos.
We've been monitoring
the Moravianos for quite some time.
We only recently made a breakthrough.
When we turned Mikoy into an asset.
You convinced Mikoy to become an asset?
I must say, your powers
of persuasion are impressive.
Well, it was more like
the power of desperation.
I'm sorry. I'm very desperate,
Mr. Pinagpala.
Was what we did right?
But if we did nothing,
more innocent people would suffer
because of the crimes committed
by the Moravianos and Viktor.
Mikoy is just a simple man.
When it comes to doing what's right
for the greater good,
that's where he stands.
And he's willing to do anything
for the well-being of the people he loves.
And in fact, Judge,
Mikoy took a bullet for Chiara.
This happened during a major event
hosted by the Valtrovis.
Move!
They were attacked and disrupted
by a local syndicate,
the Sinigang Cartel.
And we believe that was when their love
for each other deepened.
And if you think their love story
is already complicated,
wait, there's more.
Because Chiara Valtrovi
isn't just a rich, spoiled nepo baby.
She herself is the most powerful
of all the Moravianos.
Yes, that's correct.
She earned that title
because of her extraordinary talent
in everything she does.
See?
Even you got shocked, Judge.
That was exactly my reaction at first.
When the lovebirds finally
learned each other's secrets,
here's what happened.
The whites got mixed with the coloreds.
A major confrontation, a major chase,
and a major shootout.
Just like that scene
from Mr. and Mrs. Smith.
After all the shooting and fighting,
in the end,
they couldn't bring themselves
to kill each other.
Because they had truly fallen in love.
Right?
And this is the point
where our asset, Mikoy, defected.
Mikoy.
Those two really have quite
the far-fetched love story.
And Special Agent Alex,
our best and brightest agent,
tracked them down in Hong Kong
and successfully captured
the lovebirds in their cage.
Your petition has already
been submitted to the court.
The higher-ups will decide
whether or not to grant you immunity.
Thank you very much, Alex.
We owe you our lives.
Thank you so much.
And because the two of them believe that
anything is possible through love,
they are asking for immunity.
Immunity in exchange
for something valuable,
a very significant piece of information.
According to them, this is the formidable
enemy we should prepare for
because Concordat's plan
is to invade the Philippines.
But no,
because this Concordat
is more than capable of destroying
everything we have.
They could send us back
to the colonial era.
Appealing to your office
to grant immunity to Mikoy and Chiara.
What happens if our petition is denied?
What will happen to us?
Well, I'll just do what I have to do.
I'll arrest both of you
and bring you back to the Philippines.
What about Mom and Dad?
If your immunity petition is denied,
it will be much harder to protect
your parents, Chiara.
But if we are granted immunity,
can't we also petition the court
for Uncle Viktor and Aunt Donabel as well?
We can try, but let's cross that bridge
when we get there.
Let's focus first
on what happens to you two.
After that long presentation,
you're asking me to protect
this couple, Chiara and Mikoy?
There are so many urgent matters
in this country.
What? Got any news?
Still nothing.
It depends.
It's on a case-by-case basis.
Didn't I tell you?
Anything is possible!
All right, Mr. Everything Is Possible.
Sorry.
Alex! What are you doing?
Hey!
Chiara!
Alex, what are you doing?
- I'm sorry, Mikoy. I have no choice.
- Chiara, wake up!
I have to turn you in.
What?
Chiara! Chiara, wake up! Chiara!
Oh…
Are you even used to working in the heat?
I'm telling you, you won't get any rest.
- You won't even have time to sit down.
- True.
I'm not trying
to discourage you, okay, Sofie?
But are you really sure
this is what you want?
Hello!
Hey, have mercy on me!
Let me out of here!
Mom!